Guide to the Boardwalk Hotel and Casino Records
2016 The Regents of the University of Nevada. All rights reserved.
TEST Repository
Boardwalk Hotel and Casino Records
1995-2005
TEST Repository
MS-00093
4.5 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
The Boardwalk Hotel and Casino records, dating from 1995 to 2003, contain two security and exchange documents, promotional and entertainment materials, player's club information and photographs. Also included are plans for an operational tracking system of players.
Scope and Contents Note
The Boardwalk Hotel and Casino records, dating from 1995 to 2003, contain two security and exchange documents; promotional and entertainment materials; player’s club information; and photographs. Also included are plans for an operational tracking system of players.
Access
Acquisition Note
Arrangement
Materials are arranged with general information files first, followed by subject files in alphabetical order.
Boardwalk Hotel and Casino
- Photographs
  - Promotional photographs: exteriors, undated (Box 03, Folder 01)
  - Promotional photographs: interiors, undated (Box 03, Folder 02)
  - Slides: interiors and exteriors, undated (Box 03, Folder 03)
  - Promotional photos, undated (Box 03, Folder 04)
  - Snapshots and Polaroids, 1996 (Box 03, Folder 05)
  - Photographic negatives: promotional, exteriors and interiors, undated (Box 03, Folder 06)
- Promotional materials
  - Menus and food signage, 1998 (Box 04, Folder 01)
  - Boardwalk Logo Sign, 2005 (Box 04, Folder 02)
  - Logo Advertising Promo Copy, 1990-2000 (Box 04, Folder 03)
  - Marketing Mailings, 1999-2000 (Box 04, Folder 04)
  - New Year's Events, 1998-1999 (Box 04, Folder 05)
  - Marketing Materials, 1990's (Box 04, Folder 06)
  - National Finals Rodeo Promotion and Public Relations Materials, 1999 (Box 04, Folder 07)
  - Promotional Pamphlets and Flyers, 1990-2000 (Box 04, Folder 08)
  - Champions on Ice Olympic Tour, 2002 (Oversized box 05)
  - Backstreet Boys Tour Program, 2001 (Oversized box 05)
  - Barbara Streisand Program [2 copies], undated (Oversized box 05)
  - Bon Jovi One Wild Night Tour Program, 2001 (Oversized box 05)
  - Britney Spears Calendar, 2002 (Oversized box 05)
  - Britney Spears Tour Program, 2001 (Oversized box 05)
  - Cher Living Proof: Farwell Tour Program, 2002 (Oversized box 05)
  - Crosby Stills Nash and Young: Tour of America Program, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - Golden Nugget Gambling Hall, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - Googosh Program, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - In the Flesh: Roger Waters, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - The Lion Habitat at MGM Grand Hat, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - MGM Grand Dice, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - MGM Grand Garden Arena Concert/ Special Event History, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - MGM Grand Pen, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - MGM Grand Ephemera, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - Niel Diamond World Tour Program, 2001-2002 (Oversized box 05)
  - NSYNC Program, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - Stardust Postcards, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - Tina (Turner): Twenty Four Seven World Tour Program, 2000 (Oversized box 05)
  - Zumanity Bag, undated (Oversized box 05)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated (Oversized box 06)
  - Bellagio Invitation, undated (Oversized box 06)
  - Gaming Chips and Lapel Pins, undated (Oversized box 06)
  - EFX: Starring Michael Crawford, undated (Oversized box 06)
  - Lanyard Stage Passes, undated (Oversized box 06)
  - Photos: Exteriors, Candid, 1998 (Oversized box 06)
  - The Residences: A Condominium Hotel by Turnberry, undated (Oversized box 06)
  - Viva il Sogno! Book, undated (Oversized box 06)